<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Resources on Oh, Krab!</title><link>https://ohkrab.dev/docs/resources/</link><description>Recent content in Resources on Oh, Krab!</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://ohkrab.dev/docs/resources/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Action</title><link>https://ohkrab.dev/docs/resources/action/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ohkrab.dev/docs/resources/action/</guid><description>Action resource is a custom SQL operation that will be executed.
1action &amp;#34;&amp;lt;namespace&amp;gt;&amp;#34; &amp;#34;&amp;lt;name&amp;gt;&amp;#34; { 2 arguments { 3 ... 4 } 5 transaction = true 6 7 sql = &amp;#34;...&amp;#34; 8} &amp;lt;namespace&amp;gt; - is a action namespace &amp;lt;name&amp;gt; - is a migration reference name to use when connecting to other resources arguments block (optional) - define arguments that can be used in sql as a variable, see Resource arguments for more details sql - code to be executed transaction (optional) - specifies whether to run action in a transaction (default: true) Arguments # These attributes can be used with arguments:</description></item><item><title>Migration</title><link>https://ohkrab.dev/docs/resources/migration/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ohkrab.dev/docs/resources/migration/</guid><description>Migration resource is a single migrate operation.
1migration &amp;#34;&amp;lt;reference&amp;gt;&amp;#34; { 2 version = &amp;#34;&amp;lt;version&amp;gt;&amp;#34; 3 transaction = true 4 5 up { 6 sql = &amp;#34;...&amp;#34; 7 } 8 9 down { 10 sql = &amp;#34;...&amp;#34; 11 } 12} &amp;lt;reference&amp;gt; - is a migration reference name to use when connecting to other resources &amp;lt;version&amp;gt; - name that will be used to identify migration in the database, can only be digits, alphanumeric characters and underscores up / down - migration direction, contains SQL code to be executed transaction (optional) - specifies whether to run migration in a transaction (default: true) DSL # Up/Down migration can use built-in DSL for Data Definition Language.</description></item><item><title>Migration set</title><link>https://ohkrab.dev/docs/resources/migration-set/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ohkrab.dev/docs/resources/migration-set/</guid><description>Migration Set is a collection of migrations.
1migration_set &amp;#34;&amp;lt;reference&amp;gt;&amp;#34; { 2 schema = &amp;#34;public&amp;#34; 3 4 migrations = [ 5 ... 6 ] 7} Migrations are executed in the order defined by migration set, NOT lexicographically. &amp;lt;reference&amp;gt; - migration set reference name schema (optional) - schema name where to create schema_migrations table and run migrations (SET search_path TO &amp;lt;schema&amp;gt; is executed before each migration), default: public migrations - list of migrations references Arguments # These attributes can be used with arguments:</description></item></channel></rss>